busey.com 2016-04-28

# FACTS

                                                                                                                      Rev 11/15
FACTS                    WHAT DOES BUSEY DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                     Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                         consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                         we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                         understand what we do.
What?                    The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                         have with us. This information can include:
                               Social Security number, assets, or income
                               payment history and account balances
                               credit history and credit scores
How?                     All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                         business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                         customers’ personal information; the reasons Busey chooses to share; and whether you can limit
                         this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information                         Does Busey share?          Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
                                                                              Yes                             No
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
                                                                              Yes                             No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                            Yes                             No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                              Yes                             No
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                              Yes                             Yes
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                           Yes                             Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                             No                      We don't share
To limit                       Call 800-672-8739 and select the option for customer support.
our sharing               Please note:
                          If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we
                          sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information
                          as described in this notice.
                          However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?               Call 800-672-8739 or go to www.busey.com

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?             Busey and its affiliates: Busey Bank, Busey Wealth Management,
                                          Busey Trust Company, Busey Capital Management, Inc. and Trevett
                                          Capital Partners.
What we do
How does Busey protect my personal        To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
information?                              and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                          These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                          and buildings.
How does Busey collect my personal
                                          We collect your personal information, for example, when you
information?
                                              open an account or apply for a loan
                                              seek financial or tax advice or enter into an investment advisory
                                               contract
                                              pay your bills
                                          We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                          bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?            Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                              sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                               about your creditworthiness
                                              affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                              sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                          State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                          limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an  Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
account I hold jointly with someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                                Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                          financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                              Our affiliates include financial companies such as Busey Bank,
                                               Busey Wealth Management, Busey Trust Company, Busey Capital
                                               Management, Inc. and Trevett Capital Partners.
Nonaffiliates                             Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                          financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                               Busey does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing                           A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                          together market financial products or services to you.
                                              Our joint marketing partners include credit card companies and
                                               investment companies.
